Hey, my name is Roham from RG Marketing and if you're watching
this and you run a local business there's like a 99% chance
that you're not ranking the top three on Google when people are
searching for your service in your area and it kind of sucks
because the top three get all the calls, they get all the
traffic and they're getting all the clicks to their website as well
and what's kind of even more sad is that your competitors are
outranking you but you know you could easily be there so let's
fix it.
Now to give you an idea for an average business owner in
an average city ranking in the top three is worth around a
hundred thousand dollars.
Now I don't know how much that would be in you know
pounds or euros you can do the math on that but it's
a pretty big value and you know there's two ways to get
there so I'm going to get into those.
One is by paying Google basically running ads and Google basically takes
your top three makes it a top four and places your business
at the top.
It sounds kind of weird just trust me on it so there's
one spot that's paid and that if you pay Google thousands and
thousands of dollars every month they will put you up at that
spot that is the good news.
The only bad news is that as soon as you stop paying
Google your ranking is removed immediately.
So that's the first option and that's exactly why we help businesses
rank in the top three so you can get there in the
organic top three and once you get there you don't have to
pay Google to stay there.
Now what I've done is I've put together a video specifically for
your business and basically it has three things and I'll show you
how to rank higher on Google.
You don't need any technical know-how it's pretty easy to do and
you could probably implement these immediately.
So the only thing that you have to do is that somewhere
on this page there's a little sign up box and you put
your email in there.
Basically in the email I'll send you the video and show you
exactly what you need to do the three things you need to
do to rank higher on Google.
It's free doesn't cost any money so if you like that just
sign up.
So I'm looking forward to seeing you in the next video and
just fill out the form and let's get you ranking higher on
Google.